{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow!' and like to drink milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧶 I like to play with string."},{"text":"🐈‍⬛ I have soft fur."},{"text":"🐟 I like to eat fish."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I go 'Woof!' and wag my tail. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love to chew on bones."},{"text":"🐕 I like to go for walks."},{"text":"🏡 I guard your house."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I eat plants in the water."},{"text":"🪶 I have feathers and a beak."},{"text":"🥚 I lay eggs."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I oink and like to play in the mud. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐷 I have a curly tail."},{"text":"🐽 I have a snout."},{"text":"🍎 I like to eat apples."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo!' and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I live on a farm."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"🥛 You drink my milk."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Goat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Donkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I have big ears and hop around. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I like to eat carrots."},{"text":"🐇 I have a fluffy tail."},{"text":"🌱 I live in a burrow."}],"options":[{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hamster","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I'm yellow and fluffy, and I say 'Cheep!'. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐣 I hatch from an egg."},{"text":"🐔 I grow up to be a hen or a rooster."},{"text":"🐛 I like to eat bugs."}],"options":[{"label":"Duckling","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Chick","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Gosling","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I like to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I am the biggest animal on land."},{"text":"💧 I use my trunk to drink water."}],"options":[{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rhino","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I'm the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"👑 I have a big mane."},{"text":"🐾 I'm a big cat."},{"text":"🥩 I like to eat meat."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes and live in Africa. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 I look like a horse."},{"text":"🌿 I eat grass."},{"text":"🦓 Each of my stripes is unique."}],"options":[{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cheetah","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"cosmos":[{"level":"1","type":"cosmos","question":"I am big and bright and shine in the day. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔥 I am very, very hot!"},{"text":"🌞 I make the daytime."},{"text":"💛 Everything on Earth needs me."}],"options":[{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"2","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm round and sometimes you can see me at night. I change my shape!","hints":[{"text":"🧀 Sometimes I look like a cheese slice."},{"text":"🌕 Sometimes I am big and round and bright."},{"text":"🐺 Animals howl at me."}],"options":[{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"3","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a light in the night sky, far, far away! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✨ I twinkle and shimmer."},{"text":"🌌 There are many, many of me."},{"text":"🌃 You can make a wish on me."}],"options":[{"label":"Star","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cloud","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"4","type":"cosmos","question":"I am big and round, and you live here! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌍 I have land and water."},{"text":"🏡 You can find your house on me."},{"text":"🌱 Plants grow on me."}],"options":[{"label":"Earth","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"5","type":"cosmos","question":"They are hot balls of gas that are far away. They twinkle at night.","hints":[{"text":"🔭 You need a telescope to see them better."},{"text":"💫 They make constellations."},{"text":"✨ The Sun is one of them."}],"options":[{"label":"Moons","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Planets","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"6","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a big ball that goes around the Sun. I am red!","hints":[{"text":"🚀 People might visit me one day."},{"text":"🍫 My name sounds a bit like a candy bar."},{"text":"🏜️ I am known for being dry and dusty."}],"options":[{"label":"Jupiter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Venus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"7","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a group of stars that make a picture. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"ursa 🐻 One might be a bear."},{"text":"🌌 I have a special name"},{"text":"🌠 You can use me to navigate."}],"options":[{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Constellation","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"8","type":"cosmos","question":"I am the path that Earth takes around the Sun. What am I called?","hints":[{"text":"🔄 It takes a whole year."},{"text":"🌎 I am not straight."},{"text":"🪐 Other balls of rock also take me around the sun"}],"options":[{"label":"Orbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Axis","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rotation","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"9","type":"cosmos","question":"I am the biggest planet in our solar system. I have a big red spot!","hints":[{"text":"🪐 I have many moons."},{"text":"🌀 I am a gas giant."},{"text":"🌌 My name sounds like jump... iter."}],"options":[{"label":"Saturn","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Jupiter","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Uranus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"10","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a group of many stars, gas, and dust held together by gravity. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌌 Our sun is part of me."},{"text":"💫 I can be spiral or elliptical."},{"text":"✨ I am very, very big, much bigger than Earth."}],"options":[{"label":"Comet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Galaxy","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Asteroid","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}}]}